iseeidoimake.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy – iSeeiDoiMake

iseeidoimake.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy. Contact us at if you have any questions or problems regarding the use of your Personal Data and we will gladly assist you.

By using this site or/and our services, you consent to the Processing of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Personal Data**  – any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.  
**Processing**  – any operation or set of operations which is performed on Personal Data or on sets of Personal Data.  
**Data subject**  – a natural person whose Personal Data is being Processed.  
**Child**  – a natural person under 16 years of age.  
**We/us**  (either capitalized or not)

We promise to follow the following data protection principles:

  * Processing is lawful, fair, transparent. Our Processing activities have lawful grounds. We always consider your rights before Processing Personal Data. We will provide you information regarding Processing upon request.
  * Processing is limited to the purpose. Our Processing activities fit the purpose for which Personal Data was gathered.
  * Processing is done with minimal data. We only gather and Process the minimal amount of Personal Data required for any purpose.
  * Processing is limited with a time period. We will not store your personal data for longer than needed.
  * We will do our best to ensure the accuracy of data.
  * We will do our best to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of data.

The Data Subject has the following rights:

  1. Right to information – meaning you have to right to know whether your Personal Data is being processed; what data is gathered, from where it is obtained and why and by whom it is processed.
  2. Right to access – meaning you have the right to access the data collected from/about you. This includes your right to request and obtain a copy of your Personal Data gathered.
  3. Right to rectification – meaning you have the right to request rectification or erasure of your Personal Data that is inaccurate or incomplete.
  4. Right to erasure – meaning in certain circumstances you can request for your Personal Data to be erased from our records.
  5. Right to restrict processing – meaning where certain conditions apply, you have the right to restrict the Processing of your Personal Data.
  6. Right to object to processing – meaning in certain cases you have the right to object to Processing of your Personal Data, for example in the case of direct marketing.
  7. Right to object to automated Processing – meaning you have the right to object to automated Processing, including profiling; and not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated Processing. This right you can exercise whenever there is an outcome of the profiling that produces legal effects concerning or significantly affecting you.
  8. Right to data portability – you have the right to obtain your Personal Data in a machine-readable format or if it is feasible, as a direct transfer from one Processor to another.
  9. Right to lodge a complaint – in the event that we refuse your request under the Rights of Access, we will provide you with a reason as to why. If you are not satisfied with the way your request has been handled please contact us.
  10. Right for the help of [supervisory authority](http://www.livinggreenandfrugally.com/privacy-policy/#gdpr-contact) – meaning you have the right for the help of a supervisory authority and the right for other legal remedies such as claiming damages.
  11. Right to withdraw consent – you have the right withdraw any given consent for Processing of your Personal Data.

**[Mailing List] – Information you have provided us with**  
This might be your e-mail address, name, billing address, home address etc – mainly information that is necessary for delivering you a product/service or to enhance your customer experience with us. We save the information you provide us with in order for you to comment or perform other activities on the website. This information includes, for example, your name and e-mail address.

**[google/amazon Ads] – Information automatically collected about you**  
This includes information that is automatically stored by cookies and other session tools. For example, your shopping cart information, your IP address, your shopping history (if there is any) etc. This information is used to improve your customer experience. When you use our services or look at the contents of our website, your activities may be logged.

**Publicly available information**  
We might gather information about you that is publicly available.

## **Cookie Policy for  iseeidoimake.com**

The privacy of our visitors to iseeidoimake.com is important to us.

**What Are Cookies**

As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or ‘break’ certain elements of the sites functionality.

For more general information on cookies see the Wikipedia article on HTTP Cookies…

**How We Use Cookies**

We use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave on all cookies if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.

**Disabling Cookies**

You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of the this site. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.

**The Cookies We Set**

This site offers newsletter or email subscription services and cookies may be used to remember if you are already registered and whether to show certain notifications which might only be valid to subscribed/unsubscribed users.

## **Third Party Cookies**

In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.

## **Google ads / Analytics**

This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.

For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page.

Third party analytics are used to track and measure usage of this site so that we can continue to produce engaging content. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site or pages you visit which helps us to understand how we can improve the site for you.

As we sell products it’s important for us to understand statistics about how many of the visitors to our site actually make a purchase and as such this is the kind of data that these cookies will track. This is important to you as it means that we can accurately make business predictions that allow us to monitor our advertising and product costs to ensure the best possible price.

The Google AdSense service we use to serve advertising uses a DoubleClick cookie to serve more relevant ads across the web and limit the number of times that a given ad is shown to you.

For more information on Google AdSense see the official [Google AdSense privacy FAQ.](http://www.google.co.uk/policies/technologies/ads/)

We use Google Analytics to measure traffic on our website. Google has their own Privacy Policy which you can review [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). If you’d like to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). google analytics keep this information for 14 months

Several partners advertise on our behalf and affiliate tracking cookies simply allow us to see if our customers have come to the site through one of our partner sites so that we can credit them appropriately and where applicable allow our affiliate partners to provide any bonus that they may provide you for making a purchase.

We also use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. For these to work the following social media sites including; facebook,twitter,Stumble Upon,google+, will set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site or contribute to the data they hold for various purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.

#### **Amazon**

iseeidoimake.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com. the cookie last for

or more information on Amazon cookies see the official [Amazon privacy FAQ.  **You can  Opt out **](http://services.amazon.co.uk/standards/cookies.html) **[HERE](https://www.amazon.co.uk/adprefs)**

#### **Facebook**

We use cookies if you have a Facebook account, use the Facebook Products, including our website and apps, or visit other websites and apps that use the Facebook Products (including the Like button or other Facebook Technologies).  [OPT out HERE](https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screen)

### **No advice**

This website contains general information about medical conditions and treatments.  The information is not advice, and should not be treated as such.

### **Limitation of warranties**

The medical information on this website is provided “as is” without any representations or warranties, express or implied. iseeidoimake.com makes no representations or warranties in relation to the medical information on this website.  
Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing paragraph, iseeidoimake.com does not warrant that:  
–    the medical information on this website will be constantly available, or available at all; or  
–    the medical information on this website is complete, true, accurate, up-to-date, or non-misleading.

### **Professional assistance**

You must not rely on the information on this website as an alternative to medical advice from your doctor or other professional healthcare provider.  
If you have any specific questions about any medical matter you should consult your doctor or other professional healthcare provider.  
If you think you may be suffering from any medical condition you should seek immediate medical attention.  
You should never delay seeking medical advice, disregard medical advice, or discontinue medical treatment because of information on this website.

### **Liability**

Nothing in this medical disclaimer will limit any of our liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law, or exclude any of our liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law.

### **Website Medical Disclaimer**

(1) No Advice:

This website contains general information about medical conditions and treatments. The information is not advice, and should not be treated as such.

(2) No Warranties:

The medical information on this website is provided without any representations or warranties, express or implied. We make no representations or warranties in relation to the medical information on this website.

Without prejudice to the generality of the foregoing paragraph, we do not warrant that:

(a) the medical information on this website will be constantly available, or available at all; or

(b) the medical information on this website is complete, true, accurate, up-to-date, or non-misleading.

(3) Professional Assistance:

You must not rely on the information on this website as an alternative to medical advice from your doctor or other professional healthcare provider. If you have any specific questions about any medical matter you should consult your doctor or other professional healthcare provider. If you think you may be suffering from any medical condition you should seek immediate medical attention. You should never delay seeking medical advice, disregard medical advice, or discontinue medical treatment because of information on this website.

(4) Limiting Our Liability:

Nothing in this medical disclaimer will:

(a) limit or exclude our liability for death or personal injury resulting from negligence;

(b) limit or exclude our liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation;

(c) limit any of our liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or

(d) exclude any of our liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law.

(5) This Disclaimer:

Hopefully that has clarified things for you and as was previously mentioned if there is something that you aren’t sure whether you need or not it’s usually safer to leave cookies enabled in case it does interact with one of the features you use on our site. However if you are still looking for more information then you can contact us through one of our preferred contact methods.

We use your Personal Data in order to:

  * provide our service to you. This includes for example registering your account; providing you with other products and services that you have requested; providing you with promotional items at your request and communicating with you in relation to those products and services; communicating and interacting with you; and notifying you of changes to any services.
  * enhance your customer experience;
  * fulfil an obligation under law or contract;

We use your Personal Data on legitimate grounds and/or with your Consent.

On the grounds of entering into a contract or fulfilling contractual obligations, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to identify you;
  * to provide you a service or to send/offer you a product;
  * to communicate either for sales or invoicing;

On the ground of legitimate interest, we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to send you personalized offers* (from us and/or our carefully selected partners);
  * to administer and analyse our client base (purchasing behaviour and history) in order to improve the quality, variety, and availability of products/ services offered/provided;
  * to conduct questionnaires concerning client satisfaction;

As long as you have not informed us otherwise, we consider offering you products/services that are similar or same to your purchasing history/browsing behaviour to be our legitimate interest.

With your consent we Process your Personal Data for the following purposes:

  * to send you newsletters and campaign offers (from us and/or our carefully selected partners);
  * for other purposes we have asked your consent for;

We Process your Personal Data in order to fulfil obligation rising from law and/or use your Personal Data for options provided by law. We reserve the right to anonymise Personal Data gathered and to use any such data. We will use data outside the scope of this Policy only when it is anonymised.

We might process your Personal Data for additional purposes that are not mentioned here, but are compatible with the original purpose for which the data was gathered. To do this, we will ensure that:

  * the link between purposes, context and nature of Personal Data is suitable for further Processing;
  * the further Processing would not harm your interests and
  * there would be appropriate safeguard for Processing.

We will inform you of any further Processing and purposes.

We do not share your Personal Data with strangers. Personal Data about you is in some cases provided to our trusted partners in order to either make providing the service to you possible or to enhance your customer experience. We share your data with:

**Connected third parties:**

  * **[Google]**
  * **[Amazon]**
  * **[Mailchimp]**

We only work with Processing partners who are able to ensure adequate level of protection to your Personal Data. We disclose your Personal Data to third parties or public officials when we are legally obliged to do so. We might disclose your Personal Data to third parties if you have consented to it or if there are other legal grounds for it.

We do our best to keep your Personal Data safe.  We use safe protocols for communication and transferring data (such as HTTPS). We use anonymising and pseudonymising where suitable. We monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks.

Even though we try our best we can not guarantee the security of information. However, we promise to notify suitable authorities of data breaches. We will also notify you if there is a threat to your rights or interests. We will do everything we reasonably can to prevent security breaches and to assist authorities should any breaches occur.

If you have an account with us, note that you have to keep your username and password secret.

### **Children**

We do not intend to collect or knowingly collect information from children. We do not target children with our services.

We use cookies and/or similar technologies to analyse customer behaviour, administer the website, track users’ movements, and to collect information about users. This is done in order to personalise and enhance your experience with us.

A cookie is a tiny text file stored on your computer. Cookies store information that is used to help make sites work. Only we can access the cookies created by our website. You can control your cookies at the browser level. Choosing to disable cookies may hinder your use of certain functions.

**We use cookies for the following purposes:**

  * Necessary cookies – these cookies are required for you to be able to use some important features on our website, such as logging in. These cookies don’t collect any personal information.
  * Functionality cookies – these cookies provide functionality that makes using our service more convenient and makes providing more personalised features possible. For example, they might remember your name and e-mail in comment forms so you don’t have to re-enter this information next time when commenting.
  * Analytics cookies – these cookies are used to track the use and performance of our website and services
  * Advertising cookies – these cookies are used to deliver advertisements that are relevant to you and to your interests. In addition, they are used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement. They are usually placed to the website by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. These cookies remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.

You can remove cookies stored in your computer via your browser settings. Alternatively, you can control some 3rd party cookies by using a privacy enhancement platform such as [optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/#!/) or [youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/). For more information about cookies, visit [allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

We use Google Analytics to measure traffic on our website. Google has their own Privacy Policy which you can review [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). If you’d like to opt out of tracking by Google Analytics, visit the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

Email: admin@iseeidoimake.com

We reserve the right to make change to this Privacy Policy.

## Request User Data

Below we show you all of the data stored by iseeidoimake.com on iseeidoimake.com Select the data you wish the site owner to anonymise so it cannot be linked to your email address any longer. It is the site’s owner responsibility to act upon your request. When your data is anonymised you will receive an email confirmation.  

Last modification was made 20/05/2018
